our movie screen test take one Arturo
Castro reading for innocent girl who
gets killed first music oh what am i
doing right now I'm just about to take a
super sexy shower because my parents
aren't home and I don't know how to lock
the door I'm sorry who is this again
minority character would die second
degree are these really the luck yeah
hey my what amigos I'm going down to the
cellar to get some services I'll come
back completely unharmed okay see you in
a bit I'm sorry that's it that there's
no dollars disappearing as them Oh
creepy dude whose warning is ignored
take four you'll be wanting to stay away
from the lake house there's a killer on
the loose
oh you think I'm a murderer because I
felt like this well I didn't get to
choose my own voice okay when has the
janitor ever been the killer mmm douche
is oblivious to danger take two whoa
guys I figured it out okay listen up the
only way to stop this killer is simply
all bone in this tent right now the
janitor said so man here oh the killer
take one you should have all just had
sex in the turns
none of this would have happened wait so
the douchebag was right Cindy brought
you want to live
you